http://www.sew4less.com/privacy_policy.php

Shipping will not increase after the first item - No matter how many items you buy!
Search by PART NUMBER:
Shopping Cart
Quick Search:
All
KNIFE FOR CUTTER R-CT10-L A BLOW OUTA Word of PromiseBaby Crafted Items
Bed Cushions & Suction CupBelts - Motor & TimingBelts by lengthBlindstitch Curved NeedlesBobbinBobbin CaseBobbin Cover & Slide PlateBobbin Tire & O RingBobbin WinderBobbins PrewoundBrushes - CarbonBulbs & Light SocketCabinet PartsCam DisksChalk Check SpringsCylinder CoverExtension Plate & Free-Arm PieceFeed Dog & Feed / Darning Covers & PlatesFeet - BerninaFeet - Presser- Sewing MachinesFixed Blade Foot control and light blockFoot Controls & Power CordFusesGears for MachinesGrease & OilHand Wheel & ClutchHook & RaceHoops &
Frames - QuiltingHoops - EmbroideryIndustrial -
Bobbin CaseIndustrial -
Needle PlatesIndustrial - BobbinsIndustrial - Feed DogIndustrial - NeedlesIndustrial - Serger - Blade & LooperIndustrial Feet - PresserIndustrial Instruction Manuals SingerIndustrial Motor BeltsIndustrial-Needle Clamp, ScrewsIroning Board - AccessoriesIroning Board - Covers and PadsKnee ControlsKnobs-Reverse, Stitch Width/LengthLever ReverseManuals - Instruction & OwnersManuals - Parts List BreakdownManuals - Service & RepairMotors & ModuleNeedle Bar Needle Clamp & Needle ScrewsNeedle GuardNeedle Plates - Sewing Machines, SergersNeedle ThreaderNeedles - DarningNeedles - Sewing MachineNeedles - Singer MachineNotions QuiltingOther ItemsParts and RequestsPC BoardPortable CasesPosition Bracket Position FingerPresser Bar LifterPresser Bar PartsPresser Foot ScrewRotary Cutters, Blades, & SharpenersScissorsScrew Needle PlateScrews & WashersSeam GuideSerger - Blades & LoopersSerger - FeetSerger - NeedlesSewing CabinetSewing KitsSleeve Boards Covers & PadsSlide Plate SpringSpool Cap & Spool PinSteam Press Covers and PadsSteam Press PartsStitch Finger / Width Former / Chaining TongueSwitches
Foot Control Switches On /OffTake-Up LeverTelescopic PipeTension AssemblyTension PartsThreadThread CassetteThread CutterThread GuideThread StandsToolsTupperware Consultant Need Income
Select a Brand
AdlerAlcoAlphasewAnkerArcher
ArtisanAtlasBabylock
Bernette
Bernina
BlindhemmerBrother
ChandlerClassic
ColumbiaConsew
FAFantasiaFeiyueFinesseFunLockGammillGemsyGood HousekeeperHappylockJaguar
Lewis BlindstitchLow ShankMaierMammylockMeisterMerrowMinilockMitsubishiMontgomery WardMorse
TaconyTacsewThompson MiniwalkerToyotaTreadleTuffy LockUnion SpecialUniversal
US BlindstitchVikingWhite
Yamata
Sew4Less.com Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address,
phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor  information,
and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies
and how we use them.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback
we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company
for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product
or service requested by the customer.
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used
to send you information and updates
pertaining to your order.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates,
related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from
receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer
(SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized
with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored
on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through
your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and
capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can
choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off,
some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by
contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or
servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your
information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect
ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third
party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the
content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any
feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online
Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your
consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any
information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at
least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected
offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
HOME | Quick Search | Newsletter | Contact Us | Returns | Shopping Cart | Privacy Policy | Sitemap
Website Design by Susan Newman Design ~ Website Development by Cerulean Pixel
Copyright © 2002 - 2020, Sew 4 Less   (FT)
